https://www.ventanaresearch.com/privacy

Ventana Research Privacy Policy
We at Ventana Research respect a visitor’s right to privacy. We collect and use information as disclosed in this privacy policy statement and can notified about any issues at privacy@ventanaresearch.com.
Information Collection and Use Ventana Research collects information from our website for the purpose of conducting research, advisory and consulting services. We use this information to understand how to provide you the most relevant research and services. We may use this information to pro-actively contact you with information about our company and partners or to participate in research that we conduct on a routine basis.
Research Registration and Surveys Ventana Research offers a voluntary registration process that is used to collect information about you and your company demographics for our research. This information is used for building research panels that are for conducting research in where we will contact you to fill out surveys. The option to participate in our research is voluntary and you can be removed from our list at anytime. This information is also used to deliver research results back to you as complementary services for participation.
Advisory Services Registration Ventana Research offers a voluntary registration process that is used to collect information about you and your company demographics for signing you up for advisory services. This information is used for building research panels that are for conducting research in where we will contact you to fill out surveys. The option to participate in our research is voluntary and you can be removed from our list at anytime. This information is also used to deliver research results back to you as complementary services for participation.
Communication To Ventana Research Ventana Research offers a voluntary method to provide feedback to our company and industry analysts about our research, advisory services and consulting. This communication in electronic or hard copy form may be made public and any information that is intended to be confidential should be explicitly identified. We may retain the communications as a means to improve our business in the market. Communication from Ventana Research Ventana Research will periodically communicate with you about our research and services. This communication is critical for us to provide the most relevant research and services. If you desire to be removed our communication you can do so by providing us your contact information.
Security We use all reasonable precautions to protect personal information in a secure fashion. This information includes contact and credit card information. Only employees or authorized contractors or partners are allowed to use the information if deemed as part of their job.
Links Our web sites contain links to other sites. Ventana Research is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information.
Information Sharing and Disclosure We do not share personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our products and services and which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without permission.
We may share aggregate information, which is not personally identifiable, with others. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information.
Contact Information We at Ventana Research can be contacted via mail or through electronic mail for any questions or issues you have in regards to our privacy policy.
Mailing Address:1900 NE 3rd St., Suite 106Bend, Oregon, 97701-3889, USA
Contact Information:Phone: +1 (541) 940-10101Email: privacy@ventanaresearch.comWebsite: http://www.ventanaresearch.com/
JOIN OUR COMMUNITY
Join the Ventana Research Community, and we'll keep you informed on our latest research.
©2020 Ventana Research | All Rights Reserved | Privacy Statement | Design by
W3layouts
| Icons by FontAwesome
